Guide to the American Guild of Musical Artists Records WAG.209
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: General Files, 1918-1993
  - Choral Committee: Minutes, 1944-1948 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Choral Division, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Chorus Equity Association, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Chorus Equity Association, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Chorus School, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Chorus School, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Chorus School, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Christmas Parties, 1947-1949 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Cincinnati Summer Opera Association, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Cincinnati Summer Opera Association: Agreements, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - City Center Joffrey Ballet, 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - City Center of Music and Drama, Inc., 1943 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - City Center of Music and Drama, Inc., 1947-1950, 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Classification of roles: Exhibit "C", Undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Clippings, 1936-1937 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Clippings, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Clippings, 1946-1947, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Clippings: Frederick Huber, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Columbia Artists Management: Kurt Link case, 1954, 1987-1990 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Columbia Artists Management: Spoleto Festival, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Columbia Concerts Corporation, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Columbia Concerts, Inc., 1943 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Columbia Opera Company, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Committee I: Chorus, Operatic and Concert, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Committee II: Dance and Dancers, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Committee III: Soloists, Operatic and Concert, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Committee IV: Membership Education, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Committee V: Office Administration and Policy, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Committee VI: Program and Development, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Committee on Conflicts of Interest, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Committee Report, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Committees Revisited, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Concert Commission Fee, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Concert Management: History and queries, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Concert of the Year, 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Concert versions of operas, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Constitution and By-laws, 1936, 1938, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Constitutional amendments, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Convention, 1939? (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Convention, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Convention, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Convention, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: C, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Fischer, Leo, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: General, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: General, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: General, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: General, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: General, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: General, 1941-1942 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: General, Jan 1943-Jun 1943 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: General, Jul 1943-Dec 1943 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: General, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: General, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: General, 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: General, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: General, 1957, 1969, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: General, 1983-1984, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: Jaffe, Henry, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: Jaffe, Henry, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence: Jaffe, Henry, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Jaffe, Henry, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: L, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: M, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Managers, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Members, 1936, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Members, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Members, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: N, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: O, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: P, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Tibbett, Lawrence, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Tibbett, Lawrence, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Tibbett, Lawrence, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Tibbett, Lawrence, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Tibbett, Lawrence, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Tibbett, Lawrence, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Tibbett, Lawrence, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Tibbett, Lawrence, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Tibbett, Lawrence, 1947-1951 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Counsel (AGMA), 1944-1946 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Creatore, Guiseppe, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Crooks, Richards: USO, Camp Shows, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Dance collection: NY Public Library, Lincoln Center, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Dance contract, revised, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Dance Films Association, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Dance floor specifications, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Dance Theatre Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Davidson, James (Artist Representative), 1943 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Dayton Opera Festival, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Dell'Orefice, Enzo, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Disciplinary actions re: strike or picket line activities, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Earnings of performing artists: Ruttenberg report for AGMA, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Dubinsky, David, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Educational Opera Association, Inc., 1978, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Election procedures (AGMA), 1966 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Energy Crisis Committee and AGMA Ruling: Action of Board, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Equal Opportunity Employment reports, 1968-1980 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Equity Library Theatre, 1967-1970 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Eric Semon Associates, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Fact Finding Committee, 1978, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Finance Committee, 1971-1983 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Finances, 1937-1939 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Finances: Los Angeles, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Finances: Retainers, 1977-1981 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Financial Estimates, 1936-1937 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Financial reports, 1940-1942 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Financial reports, 1945-1947 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Financial reports, 1948-1951 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Financial reports, 1952-1958 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Financial reports, 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Financial reports, 1961-1965 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Financial reports, 1966-1970 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Foreign Artists Committee, 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Foreign Travel Per Diem Rates, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Future of AGMA (typescript), 1946 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Golden Jubilee Gala, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Grand Opera Artists Association of America, 1936-1937 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Grand Opera Artists Association of America, 1936-1937 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Grand Opera Artists Association of America, 1936-1938 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance, Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance, 1919-1923 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance, 1924-1927 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance, 1928-1930 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance, 1931-1933 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance, 1935-1937 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance: Agreements, 1918-1927 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance: Agreements, 1928-1940 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance: Agreements: Cincinnati Zoological Park Association, 1926-1931 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance: Agreements: German Chorus and Ballet Union, 1922-1923 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance: Agreements: Metropolitan Opera Company, 1921-1939 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance: Agreements: San Carlo Grand Opera Company, 1922-1936 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance: Agreements: Scotti Grand Opera Company, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance: Agreements: Wagnerian Opera Company and Festival, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance: Ballots, 1918-1939 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance: Clippings, Undated, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance: Executive Board, 1919-1924 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance: Executive Board, 1925-1929 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance: Executive Board, 1930-1934 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance: Executive Board, 1935-1939 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance: Finances, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Grand Opera Choral Alliance: Metropolitan Opera Company, NY State Labor Relations Board Brief of AGMA, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Grievance Committee: Choral, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Handbook for AGMA Delegates, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Handbook for Members, 1961-1974 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Handbook: Prelim to Final, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Hartley Bill data, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Heifetz, Jascha, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - History of AGMA, 1957, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Hollywood Victory Committee, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Hull, Cordell, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Immigration legislation, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Inauguration of President Johnson: Invitation to Hy Faine, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Income, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Income Tax Bureau ruling, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Insurance, Professional liability, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Inter-American Federation of Entertainment Workers, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1965-1976 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Instrumentalists' Meeting, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Interoffice Memorandum, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Iturbi, José, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Joffrey Ballet: Agreements, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Joffrey Ballet: Negotiations, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Kennedy, John F., 1959-1964 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Kennedy Center, ca.1970 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - La Guardia, Fiorello, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Letterheads, 1937-1982 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Library and Museum of the Performing Arts: NY Public Library at Lincoln Center, 1971-1975 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Life members survey, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Lindsay, John V. (Mayor), 1965 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Loans, 1938-1940 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Loans: Tibbett, 1941-1947 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Local Executive Committee Rules (retyped 1981), 1964 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - London, George: A Gala Tribute to George London, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - London Festival Ballet Trust Fund, Ltd.: Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles/Hollywood/West Coast office, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Los Angeles/Hollywood/West Coast office, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Los Angeles/Hollywood/West Coast office, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles/Hollywood/West Coast office, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Madison Square Garden: Negro Freedom Rally, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Managers/Agents: Correspondence, etc., 1980-1991 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Managers Basic Agreement: Research material collected by D. Tibbs, 1952-1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Managers: Letters and memos, 1956, 1968-1973 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Managers Committee, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Manetti, Eugenie, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Manners, Lucille, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Marcelli, Dolores, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Mario, Queena: Speech at American Theatre Council Convention, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 17A)
  - Marks Levine (consultants), 1958 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Mayer, Margery, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Mediation letters: Federal and state, 1973, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Medical leave for employees, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Meetings, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Melton, James, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Members: Admission of, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Members: Ballet and choral, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Membership, 1942-1943 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Membership applications, 1936-1939 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Membership lists, Undated, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Membership lists, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Membership log, 1936-1946 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Merger: Proposal (AGVA/AFRA), 1942 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Metropolitan National Company: Los Angeles Complaint, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Metropolitan Opera Association, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Metropolitan Opera Association, 1945-1951 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Metropolitan Opera Association: Chicago Choral Auditions, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Metropolitan Opera Association: Negotiations, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 35A)
  - Metropolitan Opera Chorus Auditions, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Metropolitan Opera Company, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Metropolitan Opera Company, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Metropolitan Opera Company: Ballet delegates, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Metropolitan Opera Company: Choristers, lists, 1942-1945 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Metropolitan Opera Company: Dues list, 1939? (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Metropolitan Opera Guild, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Metropolitan Opera House: Resolution on demolition, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Metropolitan Opera House: Sun Yat Sen Day, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Metropolitan Opera National Council: Auditions, 1965, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Miller, Blanche, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, 1936-1938 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors: Executive Board, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, and Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, Mar 1936-1939 (Film R-7427, Reel 1)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, and Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, 1940-1942 (Film R-7427, Reel 2)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, and Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, 1943-Aug 1944 (Film R-7427, Reel 3)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, and Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, Sep 1944-1945 (Film R-7427, Reel 4)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, and Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, Jan 1946-Aug 1946 (Film R-7427, Reel 5)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, and Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, Sep 1946-Jun 1947 (Film R-7427, Reel 6)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, and Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, Jul 1947-Dec 1947 (Film R-7427, Reel 7)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, and Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, Jan 1948-Jun 1948 (Film R-7427, Reel 8)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, and Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, Jul 1948-Dec 1948 (Film R-7427, Reel 9)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, Jan 1949-Jun 1949 (Film R-7427, Reel 9)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, Jul 1949-Jun 1950 (Film R-7427, Reel 10)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, Jul 1950-Dec 1950 (Film R-7427, Reel 11)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1951 (Film R-7427, Reel 12)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1952 (Film R-7427, Reel 13)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1953 (Film R-7427, Reel 14)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1954 (Film R-7427, Reel 15)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1955 (Film R-7427, Reel 16)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1956 (Film R-7427, Reel 17)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1957 (Film R-7427, Reel 18)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1958 (Film R-7427, Reel 19)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, Jan 1959-Aug 1959 (Film R-7427, Reel 20)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, Sep 1959-Apr 1960 (Film R-7427, Reel 21)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, May 1960-Dec 1960 (Film R-7427, Reel 22)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, Jan 1961-Jun 1961 (Film R-7427, Reel 23)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, Jul 1961-Feb 1962 (Film R-7427, Reel 24)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, Mar 1962-Dec 1962 (Film R-7427, Reel 25)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, Jan 1963-Sep 1963 (Film R-7427, Reel 26)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, Oct 1963-Jun 1964 (Film R-7427, Reel 27)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, Jul 1964-Mar 1965 (Film R-7427, Reel 28)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, Apr 1965-Dec 1965 (Film R-7427, Reel 29)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, Jan 1966-Sep 1966 (Film R-7427, Reel 30)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, Oct 1966-Jun 1967 (Film R-7427, Reel 31)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, Jul 1967-Dec 1967 (Film R-7427, Reel 32)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1968 (Film R-7427, Reel 33)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1969 (Film R-7427, Reel 34)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1970 (Film R-7427, Reel 35)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1971 (Film R-7427, Reel 36)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1972 (Film R-7427, Reel 37)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1973 (Film R-7427, Reel 38)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1974 (Film R-7427, Reel 39)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1975 (Film R-7427, Reel 40)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1976 (Film R-7427, Reel 41)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1977 (Film R-7427, Reel 42)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1978 (Film R-7427, Reel 43)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1979 (Film R-7427, Reel 44)
  - Minutes: Board of Governors, New York Area Meetings, Metropolitan Opera Shop Meetings, and Choral Committee, 1980 (Film R-7427, Reel 45)
  - Minutes: Choral Committee, 1944-1948 (Film R-7427, Reel 46)
  - Minutes: Membership meeting, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Modern Dance Company: Negotiations, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Monona, Olivia, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Moore, Lillian (Ballet teacher), 1943 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Morgenthau, Henry, Jr., 1948 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Munsel, Patrice, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Music publications, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Musical Art Society of Paterson, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Musicians Emergency Fund, 1939-1946 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - National Arts Bill / Howell Bill Data, 1954-1955 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - National Concert and Artists Corporation, 1942-1943 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - National Foundation on Arts and Humanities: National Endowment for the Arts, 1971, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - National Grand Opera Company, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - National Music Council, 1939, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - National Negro Opera Company, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - National Wartime Conference, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - New England Opera Company, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Negro Labor Victory Committee, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - New Jersey Opera Association, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - New Opera Company, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - New Opera Company: Eugene Conley dispute, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - New Opera Company: Rosalinda, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - New Opera Company: Rosalinda, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - New Orleans Opera House Association, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Newsletter: NW Agmascore, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - New York Grand Opera Company: Finances, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - New York State Federation of Labor, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - New York Times: Obituaries, 1969-1983 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Nichols, Lillian, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Occupational briefs: Dancers, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Occupational briefs: Instrumental musicians, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Occupational/Vocational Guidance research, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Officers lists, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Offices, leases, etc., 1973-1983 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Opera Producers and Managers Association, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Opera Workshop Committee, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Organization of AGMA, 1935-1936 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Pamphlet: "Questions and Answers about AGMA", Undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Pankey, Aubrey, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Pechner, Gerhard, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Pension and Health Funds, 1983-1993 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Pension and Health Funds, 1983-1993 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Pension and Health Funds: E. Wagner correspondence, 1984-1994 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Agreement and Declaration of Trust, 1968, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Pension financial statements, 1977-1983 (Box 12, Folder 48)